

PROFILE

I'm Dhia Eddine Falta

24 years old from Algeria. HTML Email developer and Web designer. I love creating and developing beautiful, unique responsive websites and Email templates. Also, I am very good at CMS Joomla.

Date of Birth: January 17th,1996 **Address:** IE 09 route de Tazoult, Batna; Algeria

CONTACT

PHONE:

+213 663541857

WEBSITE:

http://doudoufalta.com/

EMAII

doudou.falta@gmail.com

LANGUAGES SKILLS

English $\star \star \star \star \star \star$ Arabic $\star \star \star \star \star$ French $\star \star \star \star \star$

INTERESTS

- Swimming
- Football
- Volunteering and Humanitarian assistance
- Travelling
- Movies and Music

Visit my website For more information and works examples http://doudoufalta.com/

DHIA EDDINE FALTA

EDUCATION

• ILIMA institute, Batna

2018

Achieved a Web Development certificate of college study in web development By <u>Cégep de Saint-Félicien</u>, Quebec, Canada. Provided by <u>ILIMA institute</u>, Batna, Algeria.

• <u>University of Batna 2 and University of Batna 1</u> 2016 - 2019

For 3 years I studied three major. Science and technology at university of Batna 2 and Material Sciences, and Arts at university of Batna 1 Learned a lot of things from each major

Route De Tazoult High School, Batna

2016

(High School Degree in Sciences)

WORK EXPERIENCE

* RizkHalal.com (RizkHalal Co-founder)

2019 - Present

RizkHalal.com marketplace website/app developed by my brother Nadhir Falta Where I handled most of the Quality Assurance, marketing, and business analysis, as well as feature enhancements and planning.

❖ <u>iCar Transport & logistics</u> (Web Designer intern)

<u>2018</u>

 $3\ months$ Full-Time internship job with iCar Transport & logistics partner. Batna, Algeria

* El-Tibyan Association (Volunteer work)

2016 - Present

Part-Time organizational administrative work, Voluntary field outcomes: Educational courses, planting trees, Blood Donation...

❖ <u>Timgad informatique</u> (Computer Repair and Maintenance) 2014–2015

6 months Full-Time job Installing/Fixing Operating Systems and **Setting up** computer central units from scratch.

KNOWLEDGE

HTML Email, PHP & MySQL, SASS, jQuery, Shopify Drop shipping, Website hosting, Facebook ads/marketing, QA, Adobe Muse, Adobe Photoshop Basics

CODING SKILLS

